{
    "subject": "W\u0142adys\u0142aw_I_Herman",
    "predicate": "isMarriedTo",
    "object": "Judith_of_Bohemia",
    "human_readable": "W\u0142adys\u0142aw I Herman is married to Judith of Bohemia.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9887654781341553,
            "question": "Is Judith of Bohemia married to W\u0142adys\u0142aw I Herman?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.988359808921814,
            "question": "Is there a marriage between W\u0142adys\u0142aw I Herman and Judith of Bohemia?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9604688286781311,
            "question": "Name the wife of W\u0142adys\u0142aw I Herman."
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9540783762931824,
            "question": "Who is W\u0142adys\u0142aw I Herman married to?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9529887437820435,
            "question": "What is the relationship between W\u0142adys\u0142aw I Herman and Judith of Bohemia?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9320125579833984,
            "question": "To whom was Judith of Bohemia married?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9302937984466553,
            "question": "Who is Judith of Bohemia married to?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8811508417129517,
            "question": "Who was W\u0142adys\u0142aw I Herman's spouse?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.875464141368866,
            "question": "What is the name of W\u0142adys\u0142aw I Herman's wife?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.702303409576416,
            "question": "What is the name of W\u0142adys\u0142aw I Herman's partner?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=W\u0142adys\u0142aw I Herman is married to Judith of Bohemia.",
            "html": "yago_21435_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is the name of W\u0142adys\u0142aw I Herman's wife?",
            "html": "yago_21435_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Who was W\u0142adys\u0142aw I Herman's spouse?",
            "html": "yago_21435_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Who is Judith of Bohemia married to?",
            "html": "yago_21435_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "yago_21435_1.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_21435_20.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_21435_21.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_21435_23.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_21435_31.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_21435_35.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_21435_37.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_21435_41.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_21435_46.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_21435_74.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n\n\n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "Here is the evaluation of the triple:\n\n{\n  \"output\": \"no\"\n}\n\nExplanation:\n\nWhile there are multiple mentions of W\u0142adys\u0142aw I Herman's wives, including Judith of Swabia, there is no mention of him being married to Judith of Bohemia. In fact, one document (file_path: /Users/stefanomarchesin/Research/fshami/Rag/docs/yago_21435/re-ranker-msmarco/28.txt) states that W\u0142adys\u0142aw I Herman was first married to Judith of Swabia, and then later in 1089, he married Judith again (who is referred to as Sophia after the marriage), but does not mention a previous wife named Judith of Bohemia."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe documents support the statement that W\u0142adys\u0142aw I Herman was married to Judith of Bohemia. This can be seen in several entries, such as those found in files `1.txt` and `28.txt`."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"no\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": true,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": "is true",
            "full_ans": "0.9"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": "is true",
            "full_ans": "0.9"
        }
    },
    "final_decision": "true",
    "actual_decision": "true",
    "analysis": {
        "error_category": "caafscd",
        "error_detail": "cdscsd",
        "category": "csdcs",
        "stratum": "fwefew",
        "topic": "wefw"
    }
}